[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '手伝ます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Допомагати"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '手伝' read in word?",
        "answer": "допомога"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '閉めます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зачиняти"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '消します' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вимикати"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '開けます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відчиняти"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '急ぎます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Спішити"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '待ちます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Очікувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '止まります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зупинятись"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '取ります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Брати"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '曲がります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Повертати"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '持ちます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Тримати"
    }
]
